

Personal Info

Lublin. Polska

+48731148433

viktoriiadeveloper@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin

Portfolio

Github

Facebook

Skills

HTML5 - XML - CSS3 - Less

StyledComponents - Tailwind

JavaScript - TypeScript - React

Git - Github - Gitbucket

Gatsby.js - Next.js - VS Code

Figma - Eslint - Pretier

Magento2 - Wordpress

Teamwork

Communication

Viktoriia Rudneva

Junior Front-end Developer



Summary

I am a dedicated and aspiring Front-end Developer with two years of professional experience in the company For Better Future Software House.

I specialize in JavaScript, React, XML, Typescript, Gatsby, Next.js, Styled-components, Tailwind CSS, Figma, Magento 2.



Work Experience

For Better Future Soft House, Polska

February 2023 - Present

I specialize in React and work on web pages and online stores.

- Online store project: "Housetipster" Creating with a team from scratch a Magento 2. Worked homepage, blog page, product page.
- Project Recruitment website: "Hrk" Creating with a team from scratch using StyledComponents, React, TypeScript, and Gatsby. Worked Components Icons
- Project IT Company website: Creating with a team from scratch. Using StyledComponents, React, TypeScript, and Gatsby. Worked footer, banner, header, button, tooltip, dropdown menu, flipping cards, carousel, slider, hamburger menu.

Freelancer

October 2022 - February 2023

- Project Landing Page: "Trip"
- Project Landing Page: "Restaurant".
 I used technology: XML, CSS, StyledComponents,
 React, TypeScript.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in the application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process in accordance with Art. 6 paragraph 1 letter an of the Regulation of the European Parliament and of the Council (EU) 2016/679 of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

Languages

Ukrainian

Russian

Polish

English



Education

University of Trade and Economics

September 2005 - June 2012



Hobbies

Swimming, detective books, psychology, drawing.



Courses

Next.js From Scratch 2024, Brad Traversy (Udemy) July 2024 - December 2024

JavaScript - Complete Course (including 80 tasks), Bogdan Stashchuk (Udemy)

September 2022 - November 2022

Complete course on JavaScript + React, Author Ivan Petrichenko (Udemy)

July 2022 - October 2022

Front- End Developer, Author Ivan Petrichenko (Udemy) November 2021 - May 2022

«Git: Full course for beginners and not only NAIL ALISHEV", Udemy

August 2022 - September 2022

Course English for IT people Organizer: JumpEnd School, Udemy

September 2022 - December 2022

English for Beginners 100%! by , Timur Tregulov July 2022 - August 2022

WordPress Course - from Zero to Pro!, Udemy

October 2022 - December 2022

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in the application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process in accordance with Art. 6 paragraph 1 letter an of the Regulation of the European Parliament and of the Council (EU) 2016/679 of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).